Writing is just content for AI to steal.
Yeah, I don't think it is.
I think, as I said, I mentioned
the subconscious thing, I think
writing is, it is not just for
you because it's important
that other people read
it. I have had like people now
say nice things about my book.
I had a friend of mine just recently say
that he bought a stack of them and gave
them to his whole team and said like,
you know, this is really useful.
He also said that the book makes you
feel that you're not
alone when you're doing
project management, that other
people have had the same experiences.
I think there are lots of reasons.
I just saw today that somebody
I know from university,
who I haven't spoken to
since, liked a video of me opening
the box with my books in it.
And the smile on my face when I'm
opening the box with books in it,
I haven't
felt that good in a long time.
So I don't think it is just training AI.